CHUKWUKA JEFFERSON EZERIOHA

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Web Dev Student experienced in HTML/CSS and JavaScript with vigor and motivation to provide optimum customer experience. Adept to collaborative work environment, work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction

015172471933

arbeitchuka@gmail.com

Buckower Ring 79, 12683 Berlin

www.jace-dev.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Web Development

Oct 2023 - Till date

- SRH Univeristy of Applied Sciences
- Berlin

Bachelor Of Dental Surgery

Sep 2016 - March 2019

• University of Nigeria

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- GIT
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Critical thinking
- Communication
- Time Management

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent)

German (Conversational)

Igbo (Fluent)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tesla

Production associate

Grünheide (Mark) Current

Ensured primary tasks in assigned areas, including Synthesis, Quality Control, Post Process, and Packaging are completed properly

- Trained new employees on production procedures and safety protocols.
- Communicated effectively with supervisors and co-workers to address production issues and maintain a smooth workflow.

D2DPPE

Sales Representative

Remote NOV 2021 - MARCH 2022

Collaborated with other sales representatives, identified new business growth opportunities that grew sales by 80%, and conducted weekly reports.

- Managed a process re-engineering project to improve and consolidate end-to-end service processes; restructured communication flow among 10 departments and cut down paperwork by 75%.
- Worked with CRM to track customer data and perform reconciliation process.

Free Lance

Remote

Virtual Assistant

MARCH 2022 - OCT 2022

Provided a range of administrative and technical support to clients, including scheduling, email management, data entry, and research.

- Assisted clients with project management and organization, including creating and maintaining documents, spreadsheets, and task lists.
- Supported 5-year reform plan to improve quality, speed, and efficiency of logistical, administrative and technological services